Rosalyn Scheffel

806-252-5557

9407 19th St. Lubbock TX. 79407 🖃

rrcervania78@gmail.com ⊠

Outgoing and friendly with 10+ years of experience in customer service. I have 3 years of experience in designing and working with vinyl as well as working with online shops such as Etsy, Amazon, and Ebay. I'm always looking for ways to challenge myself and gain new skills.

Experience

2019-present

Little Acorns by Ro-Lubbock, TX- Designer/Contract Worker
Designing and printing on vinyl. Filling out orders on online shops such as Etsy, Amazon, and
Ebay. Managing inventory and creating wood orders such as birth rulers and growth rulers.

2008 - 2010

Bonnet Pet Store - Lubbock, TX - Cashier/Caretaker/Cleaner Ensured the well-being of various animals, entrusted with opening and closing duties and money control. Entrusted with new employee training. Designed and created a store contract for selling animals.

2000 - 2004

Sam Goody - Corpus Christi, TX - Shift Leader (3rd key manager) Selling and suggestive selling. Opening and closing duties. Money control in register and register updates. New employee training. Customer control. Inventory control. Store marketing, Store anime and manga specialist.

Education

2005 - 2006

South Plains College Lubbock, TX Associates in Applied Science – Design Communications Graduated Phi Theta Kappa. Graduated on Dean's List. Awarded with a Christine DeVitt Memorial Scholarship

1997 - 2001

Del Mar College Corpus Christi, TX Major Liberal Arts

1993 - 1997

Flour Bluff High School Corpus Christi, TX

Skills

I have experience and knowledge in managerial duties, detail, handling money and cashier duties as well as customer service. I'm also educated in technical skills including PC and Mac operating systems, proficient in Microsoft Office, experience in Silhouette, Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, and HTML. Studied classes in Photography, TV production, and Basic Animation.